export const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'How many ways of defining your variables in ES6?',
    choices: ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
    answer: 2,
    points: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      'Which of the following CSS Property sets the stacking order of positioned elements?',
    choices: ['z-index', 'stack-position', 'position', 'top'],
    answer: 0,
    points: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'How many elements can a valid react component return?',
    choices: ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
    answer: 0,
    points: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: 'The most used programming language for web development is...',
    choices: ['C++', 'PHP', 'JavaScript', 'Ruby'],
    answer: 2,
    points: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      'Which of the following CSS3 property can be used to allow line breaks within words?',
    choices: ['line-break', 'line-wrap', 'word-break', 'word-wrap'],
    answer: 2,
    points: 10,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: 'What does JWT stands for?',
    choices: [
      'JavaScript Web Token',
      'Java Web Ticket',
      'JavaScript Web Time',
      'JSON Web Token',
    ],
    answer: 3,
    points: 10,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: 'Which one of these is not a framework?',
    choices: ['React', 'Next', 'Svelte', 'Angular'],
    answer: 0,
    points: 10,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: 'Who created React.js?',
    choices: ['Tim Lee', 'Jordan Lee', 'Jordan Walke', 'Mark Zuckerberg'],
    answer: 2,
    points: 10,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      'Among the given statements, which statement defines closures in JavaScript?',
    choices: [
      'JavaScript is a function that is enclosed with references to its inner function scope',
      'JavaScript is a function that is enclosed with references to its lexical environment',
      'JavaScript is a function that is enclosed with the object to its inner function scope',
      'None of the above',
    ],
    answer: 1,
    points: 15,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      'Which of the following statement is not true regarding JavaScript?',
    choices: [
      'A JavaScript embedded in an HTML document is compiled and executed by the client browser',
      'JavaScript is an object-based language',
      'JavaScript is event driven',
      'JavaScript is a loosely typed language',
    ],
    answer: 0,
    points: 15,
  },
];
